quantumsafelist.com 2018-12-19

# 

**THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT DISCLOSES THE PRIVACY PRACTICES FOR QuantumSafelist.com**

**Information Collection and Use of Information**

In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is   
required to give his contact information (email address). This information is used to contact the user about   
the service and products we provide or wish to provide. We will not sell, share, or rent personal information to others.

**Security**

This website takes every precaution to protect our users personal information. When a user submits sensitive information   
via our site, the information is protected both online and off-line. Only the administrator of this site can access personal   
information of the users. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**

If a user's personally identifiable information changes, we provide a way to correct that user's personal data provided   
to us. This can be done within the member area.

**Right to Cancel**

Our users can cancel membership and be removed from all newsletters and databases. To do this a link is provided at the end of   
system generated email messages from QuantumSafelist.com, click the link and you will be taken to a web   
page where you may choose to be removed from just newsletters or the entire database.

**Site and Service Updates**

We may send the user site and service announcement updates. We communicate with the users to provide requested services and   
in regards to issues relating to their accounts via email.

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or   
not we use their information in this different manner
